The editor told me
Someone is impersonating me using my photo
Even using AI to imitate my voice
I'm selling tooth powder.
Speaks exactly like me
These are all fake
I've never sold
tooth powder
Gù chǐ sàn (transliteration)
Skin plaster
Foot Patches
Poria paste, etc.
Because his product is too bad
There is a problem with the ingredients
Only then would they steal the photos and names of celebrities
Borrowing someone else's popularity
To sell products
If this isn't a scam
then what is it?
You must not buy
I will teach you
an effective
tooth strengthening formula right away
I share it with my friends and team
They used it for many years
Can solve your dental problems
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
I want to share this episode with you
1.Change 3 things to reverse gum recession
2.Receding gums and loose teeth? Two organs may be at risk
3.Having fewer teeth than this increases the risk of dementia by 1.9 times
4.Reverse loose teeth and bad breath with this magical formula for strong teeth that saves your teeth.
5.Coconut oil mouthwash for antibacterial and gum strengthening
Change 3 things to reverse gum recession
There is a very exaggerated thing
There is a person
She ate three nougats
It actually costs ten thousand
That person
Is he a rich man from Dubai?
Or is the nougat made of gold?
He ate nougat
When ate the third nougat
heard a click.
tooth broke in half
spent 10,000 on dentures.
Ten thousand dollars flew away
Broken teeth
The most common culprit
It's gum recession.
Once the gums recede
It's hard to recover
Pay attention to these three things
Make your gums recede faster
Ignoring periodontal disease
Brushing too hard
Eat soft foods instead of hard foods
First, periodontal disease needs to be treated
Don't let bacteria enter through the gums
Periodontal disease is the gum killer
Bacteria can enter the bloodstream from the gums
Then it will quietly increase
stroke
heart disease
diabetes
risks
When you find
When brushing teeth
Will bleed
Red and swollen gums
This is the initial warning sign
Don't delay, deal with it quickly
The second thing is don't brush your teeth too hard
Strong horizontal brushing
Receding gums
Exposed tooth roots
Recommend you one
Many dentists recommend a toothbrush brushing method
Bass method of brushing
Preventing Tooth Decay
and periodontal disease
How to brush Bass method of brushing
Remember to choose
a toothbrush with soft bristles
To clean
gingival sulcus
Avoid damaging the gums
Hold the toothbrush at 45 degrees
Fits the area
where gums and teeth meet
Brush it in circles like this
Don't brush horizontally like this
Brush your teeth properly for two minutes
Inside and outside
Brush the occlusal surface
It is the real clean
Third, you should eat both soft and hard foods.
Eat soft food instead of hard food
Beware of faster gum recession
Your grandparents
Will it be like this too?
Eat noodles
Eat porridge
stewed soup
Drinking happily
If bite something a little harder,
will say "Oh, I can't bite it anymore"
can't bite it anymore and don't want to eat it anymore
This is called eating soft food and not eating hard food
I'll say it again
You eat too soft food for a long time
Chewing force of teeth
Getting worse
The gums will recede.
Do you have chewing problems?
It is recommended that you eat it three times a week
Food with a moderate hardness or softness
apple
Pear
celery
sweet potato
potato
nut
Hey, eat it.
These are slightly hard foods
Can train your chewing power
Stimulate periodontal tissue
Delaying gum recession
Receding gums and loose teeth? Two organs may be at risk
Gum problems
It's not just a dental problem
The root cause
It's your kidney
There's something wrong with your spleen and stomach.
yè tiān shì(transliteration), a famous doctor in the Qing Dynasty, said
Chǐ wèi shèn zhī yú(transliteration)
Kěn wèi wèi zhī luò(transliteration)
Teeth need to be nourished by kidney qi
Gums and spleen and stomachHuǒ qì(transliteration)
It also matters
these two body types
The gums are prone to problems.
The first is kidney deficiency
Second, the spleen and stomachHuǒ tài wàng (transliteration)
What happens to people with kidney deficiency?
Loose and sore teeth
It hurts to bite a peanut
Eat black foods
Black Food
Replenish kidney qi
black beans
black sesame seeds
Walnuts, etc.
Try them all
A very important concept
Lie down when you need to.
I said lie flat
It's not the kind of lying flat that young people talk about.
mean you should go to bed early.
The second
People with excessive spleen and stomachHuǒ (transliteration)
Often red and swollen gums
It hurts
It will bleed
Open your mouth
Ugh, that smells terrible.
Plus easy to constipate
This is the huǒ qì (transliteration) attack.
Twotuì huǒ (transliteration)tips to tell you
If you like tea, have a cup.
Chrysanthemum and Cassia Seed Tea
Qīng gān míng mù (transliteration)
You are a sweet soup lover
Go to the alley or convenience store
Buy a bowl of mung bean soup
To qīng rè (transliteration) and detoxify
Two kinds of food should not be eaten
Fried spicy food
Don't eat
Why?
Let the spleen and stomach rest first
The gums will not
Get angry at you every day
Friends who liked this episode
Those who haven't subscribed yet
Subscribe now
I will provide it to you
Various money-saving and effective health tips
Having fewer teeth than this increases the risk of dementia by 1.9 times
Don't take losing one tooth lightly.
Loose teeth
The brain may be affected.
At the age of 30
I went to the doctor because of a toothache.
The doctor recommended removing
only found out after pulled it out.
hehe
The nightmare begins
How to say
The upper teeth are gone
The lower teeth have no support
so what
It started to grow wildly upwards
The result is an unbalanced bite
Then pulled out the second one
biting something is like a tire slipping
One side is exerting force, while the other is idling
When I was in my 50s
Teeth are becoming looser
It's very, very miserable.
That's why you kept advising us
Missing teeth must be filled.
I don't want you to be like me
You thought missing a few teeth
wasn't a big deal
Big mistake
According to Kanagawa Dental College, Japan
Assistant Professor Yamamoto Tatsuo
A study published
in the American Journal of Psychosomatic Medicine.
He pointed out
Their research team
Targeting more than 4,000 seniors
aged 65 and above
Follow-up for 4 years
turn out
People with fewer than 20 teeth
and no dentures
Dementia risk
It is 1.9 times higher
than those
with more than 20 teeth.
You’re not seeing it wrong.
1.9 times
Missing teeth Loose teeth
Not only can you not bite
It's more likely that even
the head is loose
Don't avoid filling your teeth just because you're afraid of the cost.
In the end
you save money on filling your teeth.
The compensation is
Brainpower
memory
Even the dignity of life in the future
Reverse loose teeth and bad breath with this magical formula for strong teeth that saves your teeth.
Loose teeth
bad breath
People suffering from periodontal disease
Come
I'll share one with you
A centuries-old recipe
for strengthening teeth
From 3-year-old children
Even elders up to 80 years old can use it
Brush every day
Stabilize tooth roots
Protect gums
Improve periodontal disease
Let me tell you the recipe first.
You can take a screenshot of it now
Medicinal materials include
Qīng yán 5 qián (transliteration)
Shí gāo 5 qián(transliteration)
Bǔ gǔ zhī 4 qián(transliteration)
Huā jiāo 1 qián bàn(transliteration)
Bái zhǐ 1 qián bàn(transliteration)
Bò hé 1 qián bàn(transliteration)
Hàn lián cǎo 2 qián bàn(transliteration)
Fáng fēng 2 qián bàn(transliteration)
Xì xīn 1 qián bàn(transliteration)
You ask the owner of the Chinese medicine store
to grind these herbs into fine powder
in a bottle
Just save it
This is what tooth powder looks like when it is squeezed out
Let me show you
It has two uses
Getting up in the morning
You use a toothbrush
Apply a little tooth powder to your teeth
Then brush your teeth
Just like I said
That way of brushing your teeth
After brushing your teeth
Don't rinse your mouth right away
Let the tooth powder stay on your teeth
for one minute
Wash your face first. After washing your face
Rinse your mouth with clean water
The second
Apply tooth powder to your gums
Stay for 3 to 5 minutes
Finally, rinse your mouth with water
Just apply it and that's enough
I'm using tooth powder.
The effect is really good.
I'll buy it back
For my parents to use
very good
Let me tell you a story
The famous doctor in the Qing Dynasty
Called chén xiū yuán (transliteration)
In hisyī shū 72 zhǒng(transliteration)
Records inside
There is a 40-year-old man
Three teeth lost
Met a xiàng guó (transliteration) named lú (transliteration)
Lú xiāng guó 's younger brother (transliteration)
He taught this tooth powder
Gave it to chén xiū yuán (transliteration)
chén xiū yuán (transliteration)used tooth powder
After a while
Not only makes
loose teeth stronger
Even the tooth disease was cured
Eating hot pot in winter
Swelling and pain between teeth
Use this powder to wipe
The swelling will go away immediately
If the child starts using it when he is three or four years old
Continuous
Teeth will not fall out when you get old
Ha ha
No more toothache for the rest
of your life
That's amazing!
How can a mother
help her child use this recipe?
Being a mother
You can use a piece of gauze
to dab some tooth powder
Rub it on the surface of the teeth
Especially for children over three years old
Teeth are growing
at this time
The golden period for gum formation
Use this tooth powder
Make teeth cleaner
more orderly
Remember to share this great remedy
with your family and friends
Make teeth healthier
Coconut oil mouthwash
for antibacterial and gum strengthening
Use mouthwash every day
Worried about too many chemical ingredients?
Try oil pulling
Also called oil pulling
oil pulling
Can reduce dental plaque
Improves bad breath
Strengthen gums
The oil pulling is an Indian
A traditional health care method
Gargle with coconut oil
Mild taste
Lauric acid in it
The antibacterial effect is quite good
Why does oil remove bacteria?
The texture of the oil
Able to absorb fat-soluble substances
Inside the mouth
Mixed with saliva and emulsified
Helps remove bacteria and toxins
When is the best time to do the oil pulling?
When you wake up in the morning
You drink a glass of warm water first
Then start doing
1.Take a tablespoon of coconut oil
It's about 10 to 15cc
Hold in mouth like gargling
Let the oil flow through the gums and teeth
And between the teeth
2.Rinse mouth for 15 to 20 minutes
The mixture will turn milky white
3. Spit out the oil and don’t swallow it
Better spit in the trash
Avoid clogged pipes
4.Then brush teeth and rinse mouth as usual
That's it
Dear fans,
We have opened the membership channel
If you agree with Dr. Hu's promotion of Chinese medicine
The concept of taking care of one's own health
Small monthly donations are welcome
Or become a VIP sponsor
With you
We can go further
Thank you so much